adityapanwar580@gmail.com +91 7725952227 Delhi

Skills

- Team Building
- · Drive Sales Strategy
- Sales coaching
- · Conversion boosting
- · Team pipeline management

Education And Training

2017

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE: HOTEL MANAGEMENT Amity University, Dwarka, Rajasthan, Delhi

ADITYA PANWAR

Summary

Inside Sales Proffesional with 4+ years of experience and superior closing record achieved via implementation of best sales and marketing practices. Trained teams to surpass revenue, retention and referral objectives. Ace at up-selling and crossselling techniques as well as collaboration with marketing colleagues to increase revenue. Dedicated professional with demonstrated strengths in customer service, time management, and trend tracking. Good at troubleshooting problems and building successful solutions. Excellent verbal and written communicator with strong background cultivating positive relationships and exceeding goals. Fast Learning, results-oriented employee, utilizing organizational skills to drive business goals. Possessing exceptional problem-solving and analytical skills

Experience

Geekster - Senior Sales Associate

Gurugram

05/2023 - Current

- · Developed and implemented strategies to increase sales volume.
- Performed regular follow-up with existing clients to ensure satisfaction levels are
- · Resolved customer complaints in a professional manner.
- · 70+ Lakhs of revenue in 9 months

The Knowledge Academy - Senior Sales Manager

Banglore, India

08/2022 - 04/2023

- Domestic and International Market for Business Skill Courses , Project Management and IT securities
- · Gave benefit-oriented, polished presentations driving dramatic revenue growth across multiple sales channels.
- · Achieved dramatic sales increase by skillfully managing relationships and proactive sales approaches.
- · Tracked pipeline data, won vs. lost opportunities and lead response times with Salesforce CRM.
- · Resolved customer issues quickly to close deals and boost client satisfaction.
- · Managed and motivated sales team to increase revenue.

Doubtnut - SALES TEAM LEADER

Gurgaon

03/2021 - 07/2022

- Indian online education platform for K-10, K-12. Test preparations and Govt
- Exams, Leading a team of 10 agents to achieve the sales targets of 4-5 Lakhs Per
- · Overseeing performance of individual team members and the team as a whole while aligning it with company goals Implemented process improvements and best practices
- Managing, training & helping the development of team members to achieve KPIs & targets as a team Managing the structuring and closing of the deals with new
- · Drive sales through cold calling, networking
- · Audited 20+ calls on daily basis to ensure service quality and leveraging of sales opportunities
- Preparing month end reports & presentations Cold Calling Strategy.

BUISNESS DEVELOPMENT ASSOCIATE, BYJU - Buisness Development Associate

Jaipur, Rajasthan

01/2020 - 02/2021

- · With positive attitude and helpful demeanour
- · Optimised outbound calls to reach high-volumes, using voicemail automation while progressing other tasks
- $\bullet \ \ Processed \ sales \ and \ membership \ signups \ efficiently, \ driving \ productivity \ and$ customer retention
- · Weekly individual target 100+ Calls dialled everyday, Taking follow ups with the customers.

Taj Rambagh Palace - FOOD & BEVERAGE SERVICE ASSOCIATE

Jaipur, Rajasthan

06/2018 - 11/2019

- · 5 star Luxury Hotel in Jaipur with residence of Maharaja of Jaipur
- · Increased revenue by upselling fine wines and side dish options tailored to guest tastes and preferences
- · Welcomed guests with warmth and professionalism
- · Memorised customer food and drink orders with 100% accuracy
- · Supported kitchen staff by plating starters and side dishes to improve turnaround times.

Taj Umaid Bhawan Palace - INTERN

12/2015 - 06/2016

· In all of the departments (F&B services, Housekeeping, Kitchen, Learning&Development, Human Resource).